Finding Aid for the Michael Braver Collection of Americanist Material LSC.1585
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Assorted Fugitive Materials and Limited Issues of Magazines
  - We the People., A Mimeo'd Newsletter. Usually 2 to 6 pages. 8 issues. (Box 15)
    Volume 1, Issue 44: May 14, 1973
    Volume 1, Issue 45: May 21, 1973
    Volume 1, Issue 46: May 28, 1973
  - Wolff, Prof. Charles E. Americanism Seminars., 12 pages. (Box 15)
- Transcripts Of Speeches, Total 248 Pages
  - Benson, Ezra Taft. Aiding and Abetting., 13 pages (Box 17)
  - Boccardi, Bobbi at U.S.A., 25 pages (Box 17)
  - Dr. Carver, 2 pages (Box 17)
  - Hargis, Billy James. Operation Midnight Ride, 18 pages (Box 17)
  - McIntire, Carl., 25 pages (Box 17)
  - Robert Morris. No Wonder We are Losing., 27 pages (Box 17)
  - A Seminar on the Conspiracy (Birch Society), 43 pages (Box 17)
  - Strube, Bill. Program for Action "A", 20 pages (Box 17)
  - Strube, Bill. Program for Action "B", 20 pages (Box 17)
  - Walker, Gen. Edwin. Operation Midnight Ride, 30 pages (Box 17)
  - Watson, Ann at U.S.A., 25 pages (Box 17)
- Books By Americanist Authors
  - Allen, Gary. None Dare Call It Conspiracy. Concord Press: Rossmore, CA, 1971.; (2 copies). (Box 20)
  - Bales, James. J. Edgar Hoover Speaks Concerning Communism. Capitol Hill Press: Washington D.C., 1972. (Box 20)
  - Courtney, Phoebe. How Dangerous is McGovern? The Independent American: Littleton, CO, 1972. (Box 20)
  - Dobbs, Z. The Great Deceit. Veritas Foundation: West Sayville, NY, 1964. (Box 20)
  - Hargis, Billy James. Communist America ... Must it Be? Christian Crusade: Tulsa, 1960. (Box 20)
  - Hargis, Billy James. Satanic Conspiracy. Christian Crusade Publications: Tulsa, 1960. (Box 20)
  - Hospers, John. Libertarianism. Reason Enterprises: Santa Barbara, CA, 1971. (Box 20)
  - Schwarz, Fred. You Can Trust the Communists to be Communists. Christian Anti-Communist Crusade: Long Beach, CA, 1960 (1972). (Box 20)
  - Stang, Alan. It's Very Simple. Western Islands: Boston, 1965. (Box 20)
  - Steinbacher, John. Bitter Harvest. Orange Tree Press: Whittier, CA, 1970 (Box 20)
  - Stone, Willis. Where the Money Went. (Box 20)
  - Liberty Amendment Committee: L.A., 1971. (Box 20)
  - Stormer, John. None Dare Call It Treason. Liberty Bell Press: Florissant, Missouri, 1964. (Box 20)
  - Welch, Robert. The Life of John Birch. Western Islands: Boston, 1954 (1965) (Box 21)
  - Welch, Robert. The Blue Book of the John Birch Society. Western Islands: Boston (Belmont), Mass, 1959 (1961). (Box 21)
  - Wolff, Charles. Freedom is Not Free II. C.E. Wolff: Long Beach, CA, 1971 (Box 21)
- Critical and Academic Analyses of Americanism
  - Chalmers, David. Hooded Americanism. Chicago: Quandrangle, 1968. (Box 21)
  - The Dixon Line - Volumes 10, 11 and 12., 17 issues. (Box 19)
    An Anti-Extremist Newsletter.
    Volume 10, issue 1: November 1972 to December 1972
    Volume 10, issue 2: January 1973
    Volume 10, issue 3,4: February 1973 to March 1973
    Volume 10, issue 5: April 1973
    Volume 10, issue 6: May 1973 to June 1973
    Volume 10, issue 7: July 1973
    Volume 10, issue 8: August 1973
    Volume 10, issue 9: September 1973
    Volume 10, issue 10: October 1973
    Volume 11, issue 1: November 1973
    Volume 11, issue 2: December 1973 to January 1974
    Volume 11, issue 3: March 1974 to April 1974
    Volume 11, issue 5: July 1974 to August 1974
    Volume 11, issue 6: September 1974 to October 1974
    Volume 12, issue 1: November 1974 to December 1974
    Volume 12, issue 2: January 1975 to February 1975
    Volume 12, issue 3: March 1975 to April 1975
    Volume 12, issue 4: May 1975 to June 1975
  - Group Research Report, Volume 11, No. 11. (Box 19)
  - Hotbed of Hatred., May 21, 1965. (Box 19)
    Transcript of KLAC (Los Angeles) Special Report on Political Extremism in Southern California. Also, tapes (2 cassettes).
  - Journal Of Social Issues, entire volume devoted to "American Political Extremism in the 1960s." Volume XIX, Issue 2., April 1963.; Worn Condition. (Box 16)
  - Solara, Ferdinand. Key Influences in the American Right. Polifax Press: Denver., 1972. (Box 21)
- Cassette Tapes
  - Abraham, Larry. (T.R.A.I.N.) China and Asia History. Honolulu., August 15, 1971.; (2 tapes) (Box 12)
  - Abraham, Larry. Where Do We Go From Here or The Two Big Lies of Communism. Tacoma, WA., April 11, 1971. (Box 12)
  - Allen, Gary. The John Birch Society Confronts the Issues of 1972. Los Angeles, October 14, 1972. (Box 14)
  - Anderson, Tom. A.I.P. Campaign Speech. Hollywood, CA., March 5, 1973. (Box 13)
  - Anderson. American Independent Party Keynote Speech. Buena Park, CA., August 5, 1972. (Box 13)
  - Anderson. For Christians--Put on the Whole Armor of God. Boston., July 3, 1972 (Box 13)
  - Batema, Rev. Ray. How and Why our Churches must stand against Communism. Tulsa., August 3, 1973. (Box 12)
  - Batema, Rev. Satan's Bid for Your Kid. Pomona, CA., 4th Sunday of October 1971. (Box 12)
  - Bean, (Dr.) J. Narcotics. Glendale, CA, September 25, 1969. (Box 14)
  - Beeny, Wm. Communist World Offensive. Los Angeles, November 7, 1970.; (2 tapes) (Box 12)
  - Boccardi, Bobbi. H.O.W. Encino, CA., January 22, 1973. (Box 14)
  - Bradley, Gene. The National Council of Churches., Spring 1963. (Box 14)
  - Bundy, Maj. Edgar. The Right Wing or the Wrong Wing., July 21, 1963. (Box 13)
  - Crow, Joe. Rock Music, Drugs, Brainwashing. Renton, WA, November 4, 1970; (2 tapes) (Box 13)
  - DeVos, Rich. Selling America. For KPS Entp. Arcadia, CA. (Box 13)
  - Dunker. How the Reds took China., undated. probably early 1960s. (Box 12)
  - Fagan, Myron. Studio Recording. (Box 14)
  - Fenton, (Fr.) Francis. The Conspiracy. Berkeley, CA., June 10, 1972. (Box 14)
  - Fenton. The John Birch Society, Myth and Reality. Arcadia, CA., November 5, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Goff, (Rev) Kenneth (Soldiers of the Cross). Untitled., September 13, 1963. (Box 13)
  - Goff. When the Revolution Comes. Los Angeles., September 13, 1963.; (2 tapes). (Box 13)
  - Goff. When the Righteous Rule. Los Angeles., February 15, 1968. (Box 13)
  - Graham, Elliot. School Board Rally. Glendale, CA., March 30, 1973. (Box 13)
  - Griffin, G. Edward. The Conspiracy. Berkeley, CA., June 10, 1972. (Box 13)
  - Griffin, G. Edward. The John Birch Society Confronts the Issues of 1972. Los Angeles, October 14, 1972. (Box 13)
  - Gumaer, David Emerson. Revolution on Campus. Van Nuys, CA., October 15, 1970.; (2 tapes.) (Box 13)
  - Hargis, (Rev) Billy James. Christian Crusade Speech. Anaheim, CA, October 8, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Hargis. Watchman on the Wall. Tulsa, OK., August 4, 1972. (Box 13)
  - Hospers, John. Libertarians-T.R.U.E. Los Angeles., 4-14-73.; (2 copies) (Box 13)
  - Hurley, Patricia. The Conspiracy. Berkeley, CA, June 10, 1972. (Box 13)
  - Judd, Walter. 1973-74, Crucial Years for America. Tulsa., August 4, 1972. (Box 13)
  - Leonard, Paul. Elliot Graham for School Board. Glendale, CA., March 30, 1973. (Box 13)
  - Lyon, Bob. T.R.U.E. (Tax Protest). Los Angeles., April 14, 1973.; (2 copies). (Box 13)
  - Martin, Laurel. Elliot Graham for School Board. Glendale, CA., March 30, 1973. (Box 12)
  - Morley, John. What's Right with America. For KPS Ent., Arcadia, CA. (Box 12)
  - Noebel, David. Communism and Christianity. Tulsa., August 5, 1972. (Box 14)
  - Noebel. Erosion of America's National Service. Tulsa., undated. (Box 14)
  - Noebel. Marxist Minstrels. Tulsa., August 5, 1972. (Box 12)
  - Noebel. Modern Man in Rebellion Against God. Tulsa, OK., August 4, 1972. (Box 12)
  - O'Campo, Melchor. The Conspiracy. Berkeley, CA, June 10, 1972. (Box 12)
  - Oddorizzi, Dom. Gold, Guns, Grub and Italians. Grenada Hills, CA., 1973. (Box 12)
  - Oddorizzi, Dom. The U.N. Grenada Hills, CA., March 23, 1973. (Box 12)
  - Pedigo, Jess. Satan Worship. Tulsa., August 4, 1972. (Box 12)
  - Penebaz, Fernando. Communist Tyranny in Cuba. Ventura, CA., May 15, 1967. (Box 14)
  - Phillips, Emily. Liberals and Subversives in the P.T.A. Thousand Oaks, CA, January 7, 1965.; (2 tapes). (Box 14)
  - Phillips, Emily. The P.T.A. Thousand Oaks, CA., January 21, 1965.; (2 tapes). (Box 14)
  - Rockwell. George Lincoln. ("American Nazis"). San Diego., March 1962. (Box 13)
  - Rowe, Edward. America--Wonderland or Wasteland. Encino, CA., March 25, 1973. (Box 14)
  - Schmitz. (Hon.) John. A.I.P. Acceptance Speech. Buena Park, CA., August 5, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Schmitz, (Hon.) The John Birch Society Confronts the Issues of 1972. Los Angeles, October 14, 1972. (Box 12)
  - Schmitz. John. For Christian Crusade. Anaheim. CA., October 8, 1971. (Box 12)
  - Schwartz, Fred. (Christian AntiCommunism Crusade). Anarchism. Palo Alto CA., February 19, 1973. (Box 12)
  - Schwartz. Leninism. Palo Alto, CA., February 17, 1973. (Box 12)
  - Schwartz, Fred. Marcuse and the Politics of Sex., February 19, 73. (Box 12)
  - Schwartz, Marxism. Palo Alto, CA., February 17, 1973. (Box 14)
  - Schwartz. State of Union and Communist Conquest. Buena Park, CA., March 16, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Skousen, Cleon. The Liberty Amendment. Norwalk, CA., March 31, 1973.; (2 copies) (Box 14)
  - Smith, Charles. The Conspiracy. Berkeley, CA, June 10, 1972. (Box 14)
  - Smith, Charles. The John Birch Society Confronts the Issues of 1972. Los Angeles, October 14, 1972. (Box 14)
  - Smoot, Dan. The John Birch Society Confronts the Issues of 1972. Los Angeles, October 14, 1972. (Box 14)
  - Stang, Alan. Bad Business. Newburgh, NY., June 15, 1973. (Box 14)
  - Stang, Alan. The Conspiracy. Berkeley, CA, June 10, 1972. (Box 14)
  - Stanley, Scott. The John Birch Society Confronts the Issues of 1972. Los Angeles, October 14, 1972. (Box 14)
  - Steinbacher, John. It Comes Up Murder., undated. (Box 14)
  - Steinbacher, John. Rape and Revolution., undated. (Box 14)
  - Stone, Wills. The Liberty Amendment. Norwalk, CA., March 31, 1973. (Box 13)
  - Tax Rebellion. Multiple Speakers, Bob Lyon as M.C. Los Angeles., April 14, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Wakefield, (Hon.) Floyd. The Liberty Amendment. Norwalk, CA., March 31, 1973; (2 cassettes). (Box 12)
  - Watson, Ann. They Came in Peace. Altadena, CA., September 29, 1972. (Box 14)
  - Watson, Ann. Untitled. Encino, CA., January 22, 1973.; (2 tapes). (Box 12)
  - Welch, Robert. Through All the Days to Be. San Fernando Valley, CA., April 11, 1961.; (2 tapes). (Box 12)
  - Welch. For Christian Crusade., 1965. (Box 13)
  - Welch. Closing Speech for Christian Crusade, 1965. (Box 13)
  - Welch. The Truth about Vietnam. Studio Recording., 1967. (Box 13)
  - Wells, Rev. Bob. Can Vatican Take Jews off the Hook. Anaheim, CA., undated. (Box 12)
  - Willis, Jack. Libertarian Platform. Los Angeles., April 14, 1973.; (2 copies). (Box 13)
  - Wright, Ron. Elliot Graham for School Board. Glendale, CA., March 30, 1973. (Box 13)
  - Wright, Ron. (Local Radio M.C.) Encino, CA, February 26, 1973. (Box 13)
  - Wright, Ron. (Local Radio M.C.) San Gabriel, CA., September 24, 1972. (Box 12)
- Reel to Reel Tapes
  - Abraham, Larry. The Two Big Lies of Communism. Tacoma., April 11, 1971. (Box 24)
  - Abraham. Who is Trying to Destroy Our Local Police? Seattle., February 23, 1971. (Box 25)
  - Allen, Gary. How the Left Turned Me Right. Arcadia, CA., March 23, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Allen, Gary. None Dare Call it Conspiracy. San Marino, CA., September 10, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Amis, Herbst. Oppose Revolutionary Donations. Los Angeles., April 4, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Anchell, (Dr.) Melvin. Protesting Sex Education. Santa Monica, CA., March 28, 1969. (Box 23)
  - Anderson, (Pastor) Harold. A Study of the Book of Revelation Pt. 9; The Anti-Christ: Coming World Dictator. Somis, CA., March 26, 1972. (Box 3, Box 23)
  - Anderson, Tom. Bipartisan Treason. Pasadena, CA., February 23, 1963. (Box 23)
  - Anderson, Tom. For Christians: Put on the Whole Armor of God. Boston., July 3, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Anderson, Tom. (Pub. Farm and Ranch Magazine) The Great Society. (John Birch Society) San Jose, CA., September 16, 1965. (Box 9, Box 24)
  - Anderson, Tom. Straight Talk. Oakland, CA, March 8, 1965 (Box 9, Box 24)
  - Anderson, Tom. Straight Talk. Pasadena, CA, February 23, 1963 (Box 24)
  - Anderson. "Education." See John Birch Society Council Dinner, 1971. (Box 9)
  - Anderson. The True Meaning of Christianity. Atlanta., September 13, 1970. (Box 23)
  - Anderson. Thomas and Tex Talbert. (John Birch Society). Straight Talk. Pasadena, CA., February 23, 1963. (Box 24)
  - Armour, C. Communism and Conspiracy. Sierra Madre, CA., April 10, 1971. (Box 24)
  - Ashbrook, John. (Congressman associated with the John Birch Society). At the United Republicans of California Convention, San Jose., May 6, 1972. (Box 9)
  - Bayne, Frank. (State Citizens Councils). Untitled. Los Angeles, CA, May 9, 1967. (Box 3)
  - Bean, Joseph (Dr.). Our Schoolchildren are being Programmed. San Marino, CA., April 26, 1971. (Box 23)
  - Bean, Joseph and Eleanor Howe (National Justice Foundation). P.P.B.S. or New Methods for Mind Control. Oxnard, CA., January 27, 1972. (Box 6, Box 23)
  - Beeny, (Dr.) Bill. (Soldiers of the Cross). The Communist World Offensive. Los Angeles., November 7, 1970. (Box 24)
  - Benson, Ezra Taft. If Treason Prosper. Yorktown Heights. NY., November 17, 1971. (Box 25)
  - Benson, Ezra Taft. Major Address at the Robert Welch Testimonial Dinner (John Birch Society), Los Angeles, September 23, 1963. (Box 25)
  - Benson, Ezra Taft. Major Address at the Robert Welch Testimonial Dinner (John Birch Society), Los Angeles, September 16, 1964. (Box 6)
  - Browning, Gordon. The Policeman's Dilemma, (JBS) Grenada Hills, CA, September 17, 1970. (Box 3, Box 25)
  - Browning. How to Extend Your Influence. (FIPo), Glendale, CA., February 17, 1965. (Box 7, Box 24)
  - Bruce. (Congressman) Donald. Untitled Talk. Los Angeles, CA, December 4, 1961. (Box 4)
  - Bundy, Major Edgar C. (Church League of America). The Biblical Case for Individualism. Canoga Park, CA., September 16, 1964. (Box 6, Box 23)
  - Bundy. The Big Lie Technique. Canoga Park, CA., September 15, 1964.; (2 copies). (Box 23, 25)
  - Bundy. Church League of America. Canoga Park, CA., March 4, 1965. (Box 4, Box 23)
  - Bundy. Communist Helpers within the United States. Los Angeles, CA., March 3, 1963.; (2 copies). (Box 8, 10)
  - Bundy. Education. Santa Barbara, CA., October 19, 1961. (2 copies). (Box 1)
  - Bundy. The Formation of the Church of the Antichrist. Canoga Park, CA., March 1, 1966. (Box 1, Box 23)
  - Bundy. The Here and Now Church. Anaheim, CA., August 10, 1969. (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Bundy. Looking for the Light of the World. Anaheim, CA, March 13, 1966. (Box 1, Box 23)
  - Bundy. Modernism, Communism's Most Effective Ally. Anaheim, CA., March 11, 1966.; (2 copies). (Box 2)
  - Bundy. Religion. Santa Barbara, CA., October 18, 1961.; (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Bundy. [The] Right Wing or the Wrong Wing. Anaheim, CA., July 21, 1963. (Box 8)
  - Bundy. [And] Should Communism Be Victorious? Anaheim, CA., March 13, 1966. (Box 1, Box 23)
  - Bundy. Socialist Substitute for Salvation. Anaheim, CA., August 10, 1969. (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Bundy. The State Department. Santa Barbara, CA., October 17, 1961.; (2 copies). (Box 1)
  - Bundy. [The] Unholy Coalition to Destroy Christianity. Los Gates, CA., March 28, 1965. (Box 8)
  - Bundy. The U.S.S.R. Santa Barbara, CA., October 10, 1961.; (2 copies) (Box 1)
  - Bundy. Will the American Republic Die Through Brainwashing. Canoga Park, CA., September 17, 1964. (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Caldwell, Taylor. Yellow Travelers. (Christian Crusade) Tulsa., 1966. (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Capell, Frank. the Communist Threat from Within. Los Angeles., June 18, 1964. (Box 24)
  - Capell. Subversives in the U.S. State Dept. 3rd Wed. of April., 1970. (Box 23)
  - Capell. (Liberty Lobby) "The Untouchables." Los Angeles., October 23, 1971.; (2 copies). (Box 1)
  - Caradja, Catherine (Rumanian Princess). The Worth of Freedom. San Jose, CA., March 22, 1966. (Box 25)
  - Carto, Willis. (Liberty Lobby). Govt. Politics: A Christian Crusade., 1961. (Box 23)
  - Castro, Juanita. Communism, Castro and Cuba. (CACC). Anaheim, CA., February 19, 1972. (Box 10, Box 23)
  - Chao, Dr. Calvin. (Pres. chinese for Christians, Inc.) Christian Freedom vs. Communist Totalitarianism. Hollywood, CA., June 12, 1961. (Box 25)
  - Chen, John. (T.R.A.I.N. - JBS). China. Grenada Hills, CA., March 1, 1973. (Box 24)
  - Clark, (Sheriff) Jim. Selma, Alabama. Los Angeles, CA., May 9, 1967. (Box 3, Box 25)
  - Colbert, James. Communism }n Asia. Los Angeles., November 8, 1960.; (2 copies). (Box 2, 4, Box 24)
  - Colbert, James.(CACC) Communist Crises in Asia and India. Los Angeles, August 29, 1962. (Box 4, Box 24)
  - Comparet. Bertrand L. (Christian Vanguard or New Christian Crusade Church). "Benjamin." San Diego, CA., September 1967 or October 1967. (Box 6, Box 25)
  - Comparet. Jerusalem; A Cup of Trembling. San Diego., November 1967. (Box 6, Box 25)
  - Comparet. The Glory of God. San Diego., December 1967. (Box 25)
  - Comparet. The Great Assize., December 1967. (Box 5, Box 25)
  - Comparet. Pre-recorded Tapes/Messages for the New Christian Crusade Church. E.g.: "God Commands Racial Segregation," "Man and Beast" etc., 1960s. (Box 8)
  - Cotton, Richard. The Silver Situation. Los Angeles., February 22, 1968. (Box 23)
  - Crane, (Dr.) George. Psychology of the Left Wing, Glendale, CA., April 8, 1967. (Box 4, Box 23)
  - Crane, Stuart. Man and Equality. Cherry Valley, CA., January 15, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Crane. Man and Evolution. Cherry Valley, CA., January 15, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Crane. Man and Money. Cherry Valley, CA., January 16, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Crane, Stuart. Proofs of a Conspiracy. Long Beach, CA., May 17, 1969. (Box 24)
  - Crane, Stuart. The Relationships of Man. Cherry Valley, CA., January 15, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Crane. French Revolution and U.S. Civil War. Cherry Valley, CA., January 15, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Crane. The Salt of the Earth. Cherry Valley, CA., January 15, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Crane. The Shopping Center: Man, War, and World Government. Cherry Valley, CA., January 15, 1972. (Box 24)
  - Crow, Joe. Rock Music, Drugs and Brainwashing. (TACT). Renton, WA., November 4, 1970. (Box 23)
  - Dall, (Col.) Curtis. (Liberty Lobby for Christian anti-Communist Crusade). What the People must Tell their Legislators. Tulsa., August 3, 1968. (Box 4)
  - Dean, Douglas. Another Look at Genesis. Glendale, CA., April 1, 1967.; (2 copies). (Box 11, 23, 24)
  - Dean, Douglas. Darwinism and Marxism. Glendale, CA., April 1, 1967.; (2 copies). (Box 11, 23, 24)
  - Dean, Douglas. Scientific Mind and Evolution. Glendale, CA., April 1, 1967.; (2 copies). (Box 11, 23, 24)
  - Dennis. Rev. Delmar. (JBS), I was in the KKK for the FBI. Burbank., April 6, 1968. (Box 6, Box 24)
  - Dennis, D. (JBS, Pre-recorded). The Will and The Way to Win. Fort Lauderdale, 1972. (Box 6)
  - DePauw, (Fa.) Gommar. What in the name of God is Happening to Our Church? Sepulveda, CA., February 18, 1967. (Box 9, Box 23)
  - DePugh, Robert B. (Minutemen). Untitled. Los Angeles., October 30, 1962. (Box 25)
  - Dewey, Leo. Report of General Walker. Oxford, Miss., October 10, 1962. (Box 25)
  - Diamond, Carol. (Liberty Lobby). Up to Date in Washington, Los Angeles., October 23, 1971. (Box 1)
  - Dilling, Elizabeth. (Soldiers of the Cross). Evergreen, CO., July 26, 1965. (Box 25)
  - Dinsmore, Herman. Distorted News. Santa Barbara, CA., February 27, 1970. (Box 2)
  - Dodd, T. America's Internal Security. (CACC) Los Angeles, CA., August 28, 1961. (Box 5, Box 24)
  - Donati, James. (Ch. CA Committee for Economic Freedom). the Liberty Amendment. Los Gatos, CA., 1962. (Box 5, Box 6)
  - Drew, (Dr.) Elmer M.D. Mental Health. San Francisco., August 28, 1964. (Box 8, Box 23)
  - Duberrier, H. Americanism Class (JBS): Vietnam, Why Not Win. Burbank, CA., December 14, 1969. (Box 5, Box 24)
  - Dunner, (Dr.) Joseph (Yeshiva University). Communism: the Enemy of the Jewish People. (CACC). Anaheim, CA., February 20, 1972 (Box 10, Box 23)
  - Elfman, Herbert. (Jewish Society of Americanists, John Birch Society). Is the John Birch society Anti-Semitic? Thousand Oaks, CA., July 22, 1968. (Box 6, Box 25)
  - Everingham, JFK, Keynes, and The Fabians. christian Crusade., 1961. (Box 23)
  - Everingham, Harry T. (President We the People). What the american People Need to Know in Time to Save Themselves from a Communist Takeover. We the People All American Conference, Phoenix, AZ., October 23, 1970. (Box 2)
  - Fenton, Father Francis. The John Birch Society: Myth and Reality. Arcadia, CA., November 5, 1971. (Box 9)
  - Forth, Arthur J. Taxes, Los Angeles., April 4, 1970. (Box 8)
  - Frank, Steve. (V.I.V.A.) Hypocrisy of the New Left. Ventura, CA., October 9, 1969. (Box 8, Box 23)
  - Goff, Reverend Kenneth. (Soldiers of the Cross) From Autocracy to Anarchy. Los Angeles., February 14, 1968. (Box 5, Box 24)
  - Goff. Communism in the Churches. Los Angeles., July 24, 1961. (Box 10, Box 24)
  - Goff. The Hidden Government. Los Angeles., July 29, 1961. (Box 10, Box 24)
  - Goff. When the Righteous Rule, the People Rejoice. Los Angeles., February 15, 1968. (Box 5, Box 24)
  - Goff. Survival When the Revolution Comes. Closed Meeting. Los Angeles., September 13, 1969. (Box 6, Box 24)
  - Goff. World Government. Los Angeles., September 13, 1969. (Box 6, Box 24)
  - Griffin, Edward. The U.N.--A Fearful Master. San Jose, CA., May 26, 1965. (Box 24)
  - Griffin, Edward. (JBS). A Second Look at the U.N. Glendale, CA., May 10, 1970. (Box 3, Box 24)
  - Gumaer, David. Revolution on Campus. Burbank, CA., October 15, 1970. (Box 23)
  - Gumaer, David. Revolution on Campus. Van Nuys, CA., October 15, 1970. (Box 9, Box 23)
  - Gumaer. Revolution Underway. Burbank, CA., January 10, 1971. (Box 23)
  - Hampton, Commander. Report on Chicago. Los Angeles., November 8, 1960.; (2 copies) (Box 4, Box 24)
  - Happiness of Womanhood (H.O.W.). Multiple Speakers, "A Satin Pillow Rally." Los Angeles., August 26, 1972. (Box 9)
  - Hargis, Billy James. Christian Crusade, with Matt Cuetic, Santa Barbara, CA., March 4, 1962. (Box 6, Box 23)
  - Hargis. Disarmament. Long Beach, CA., August 28, 1966. (Box 10, Box 23)
  - Hargis. Operation Midnight Ride. Oklahoma City., March 27, 1963.; Braver, Michael (Box 6, Box 23)
    - Christian Crusade Operation Midnight Ride, 1963 March 3-27; yrlsc_1585_006_001a; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:32:56) 7 inches (Box 6, Case 1)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are available for access. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
      Scope and Contents
      Transcribed from container: 3/27/63 Billy James Hargis Oklahoma City; 3/12/63 General Edwin Walker Greenville, South Carolina.
    - Christian Crusade Operation Midnight Ride, 1963 March 3-27; yrlsc_1585_006_001b; 1 Sound Recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 1:32:56) 7 inches (Box 6, Case 1)
  - Hargis. The President's Assassin Speaks., August 21, 1963. (Box 23)
    This is a canned tape made by Hargis on the Radio. Hargis superimposes questions over responses allegedly made by Lee Harvey Oswald.
  - Hargis. Signs of the times in 1972. Tulsa., August 3, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Hargis. Washington's Persecution of Christians. El Segundo, CA., May 20, 1966. (Box 2, Box 23)
  - Hargis. Watchman on the Wall. Tulsa., August 4, 1972. (Box 23)
  - Harmer, (Sen.) John. Protesting Sex Education. Santa Monica, CA., March 28, 1969. (Box 23)
  - Hays, Lee. The Pueblo. San Diego., April 1971. (Box 23)
  - Heinan, Timothy. (T.A.C.T--JBS). The Arthur Bremer Story. Santa Monica, CA., April 9, 1973. (Box 4)
  - Hess, (Dr.) George. Socialism: A Degenerative Disease. San Jose., November 16, 1965. (Box 8, Box 23)
  - Hixon. (Major General) William V. The Plan of the Secretary of Defense. Thousand Oaks, CA., March 4, 1965. (Box 9, Box 25)